[English subtitles are available]
I've shown you the way.
As for what to do,
it's up to you.
Choose the long shot of a lifetime together,
or give up the lover
for the Three Realms?
Liu Shao.
You have to make a choice.
[Chapter about Liu Shao]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 39]
It turns out that everything is already doomed.
My fate
has already been changed to the Three Realms
by the three-day agreement.
Turns out
a dramatic life
means such sacrifices.
The God of the Sun
must have felt the same way I do now.
He chose to use the Moon Sword,
in an attempt to save the Moonlight a ray of life.
So,
the God of Moonlight wanted me
to kill Luo Ge
with the Crown Wheel?
Liu Shao.
It's a cruel choice.
Should I leave you in the misery forever?
Maybe
it's the best
if I do it.
Immortal Liu Shao is back!
Tell her
I'm in retreat.
I'll take care of the arrangements.
Oh.
What's wrong, Luo Ge?
Care about your little bride?
Shut up!
Even the Moonlight can't kill me.
You think you can?
The God of Moonlight didn't kill you
because Sun's kindness.
Liu Shao's gonna kill you this time.
It's a pity you don't have time.
The Three Realms
will be mine.
Why are you still carrying it?
It's
a constant reminder of
what I did to you,
and
what I did to Luo Ning.
You don't have to wear it.
If you can keep your pure and honest heart,
it'll be enough
for me
and Luo Ning.
I'm sorry.
No matter what happens in the future,
you should remember your duty to the Demon King's bloodline.
Fu,
protecting your people
is what you do for the rest of your life.
Yes.
I know.
[Wedding]
Luo Ge.
We made a deal.
You're the only one I'm gonna marry.
I'm sure you'll come back.
Liu Shao.
He Na.
I didn't think you were gonna make it.
You're getting married to Luo Ge.
How could I not come?
But this time...
But this time to come to the Immortal Palace,
I still have some things in the demon world.
So I was a little late.
No.
I've been thinking about
getting you a big wedding gift.
And maybe this is the perfect one.
Clear Vine?
This Clear Vine was born in the extremely cold place.
It seems that it's only found in the Bone Melting Pool.
He Na.
How did you get this?
There are also places like the Bone Melting Pools
in the demon world.
But, Liu Shao, you have to remember.
To refine this vine,
it must be in the demon world.
He Na.
Thank you.
Liu Shao.
No matter what happens,
Luo Ge and I are right behind you.
Be safe.
He Na.
Do you already have a plan?
After today,
you go to the demon world,
refining the Clear Vine
and restarting the Sun Spirit.
I'm sure
Luo Ge won't leave you alone.
Okay.
Liu Shao.
From this day forward,
you are mine.
Supreme God Luo Ge.
The wedding is not yet complete.
Please behave yourself.
Don't you dare disobey me?
But...
The more you act like this,
the more I like you.
Supreme God Luo Ge
is of a noble character
and observes all manners.
Of course you don't care.
Okay.
Let's follow the etiquette.
My little bride.
Please.
Do you want to die?
Or
you want the Immortal Palace
to die with you?
Where's Luo Ge?
If you'll marry me nicely,
and serve me well,
I'll let him come out to see you.
I'm in a good mood today
and I suggest you play along.
I don't want to sacrifice their blood
on this wedding day.
Pretty,
what do you think?
Today
is my wedding day.
Don't just sit there.
Have a drink.
Pour my wine, please.
You pour the wine.
This is way out of line.
Are we just gonna sit here?
Let's just wait and see what happens.
Keep pouring.
Supreme God.
What is it?
I have one thing to report,
about the God of the Sun and Sun Spirit.
It's said that
the God of the Sun
has passed down some secrets
concerning you
by some secret method.
Secret?
I wonder
if you could walk to the Palace Chonghua for a chat.
I'd like to see
if you have any skeletons in your closet.
Liu Shao.
Wait for me.
If the God of the Sun had left behind
a secret way of dealing with this demon,
I should have seen it in the Crown Wheel.
Or...
This is what he meant
Luo Ge isn't gonna let this wedding happen?
Tell me.
What kind of secrets did the God of the Sun
tell you through secrecy?
Don't you wonder?
Ten thousand years ago,
Sun Spirit was clearly sealed by the God of the Sun,
but then
why did it wake up in Liu Shao's body?
The God of the Sun opened it in secret.
No.
I heard from Liu Shao that
it was the God of Moonlight.
Impossible.
Ten thousand years ago, the God of Moonlight...
Don't you dare plot against me?
He Na!
He Na.
He Na, please wake up.
He Na!
Liu Shao.
♫The wind is getting slower, while the pear flowers are dropping♫
Don't be sad.
♫The silver color is cold and sharp♫
I just... didn't want...
didn't want that evil thing
to hurt you
♫On the top of Heaven and between reincarnation♫
and the people
in the name of Luo Ge.
♫The moon is like snow♫
He Na.
So.
♫I carve our appointment in three days between my eyebrows♫
So I just
did what I wanted.
♫I walk through time with you♫
I didn't...
I didn't regret it.
But I regret it.
♫On the day when seas sink♫
I regret having picked up that fish.
♫When the moon never rests, the mortal world♫
Miss Liu Shao.
My name is Kho.
I'm your demon.
♫I look back to realize the dream of my next life♫
If I hadn't picked up that fish,
you wouldn't be like this
and it wouldn't be where it is today.
♫Half of my heart is yours. Half of me is missing you♫
♫I pay my life to fulfill my dream♫
♫You nag about days and nights beside my ear, but I can't hear you♫
♫The night carves the heart into poems♫
You said that
the Water Hyacinth accessory
was only for the Demon Queen.
I hope that when the curse is lifted,
you and Luo Ning
can find your own happiness.
I...
I'd love to do what you say.
Give this Water Hyacinth jade pendant
to my Demon Queen.
♫The wind is getting slower, while the pear flowers are dropping♫
Unfortunately...
♫The silver color is cold and sharp♫
Unfortunately, I...
I never
gave it away.
He Na.
♫On the top of Heaven and between reincarnation♫
I can only give it to you
as a souvenir.
♫The moon is like snow♫
Sorry.
It can no longer...
♫I carve our appointment in three days between my eyebrows♫
summon your demon.
I don't want to summon you.
♫I walk through time with you♫
I just want you to be well. He Na.
♫On the day when seas sink♫
♫When the moon never rests, the mortal world♫
♫I look back to realize the dream of my next life♫
He Na.
♫Half of my heart is yours. Half of me is missing you♫
♫I pay my life to fulfill my dream♫
Don't leave me, okay?
♫You nag about days and nights beside my ear, but I can't hear you♫
Liu Shao.
♫The night carves the heart into poems♫
Don't cry.
Your demon
is willing to
♫You left my heart. You are my fate♫
trade his body
♫You are like dreams as if you disappear♫
and his life
for
♫Two sides are round. You are like the moon at 11 pm♫
your
♫You are my fate♫
eternal
♫Look at the three realms. Look at the wilderness♫
peace.
He Na.
♫Our old fate has become a cocoon♫
♫The rest of life is no match  for a second♫
♫I look back to realize the dream of my next life♫
He Na!
♫Half of my heart is yours. Half of me is missing you♫
♫I pay my life to fulfill my dream♫
He Na.
♫You nag about days and nights beside my ear, but I can't hear you♫
He Na!
♫The night carves the heart into poems♫
Keep this pendant
close to you.
When you need me in the future,
just call out my name
♫The night carves the heart into poems♫
and I will appear.
He Na.
What are you doing here?
If you are in danger,
the Water Hyacinth will summon me.
Are you okay?
Liu Shao.
Next time you fall asleep,
remind yourself
to wake up.
Someone
loves you
and values your life
more than his own.
He Na.
Enough!
What is there to cry about?
Because your little lover
didn't kill me?
Shut up!
So.
You want to avenge He Na?
Yes.
I want to avenge He Na.
I want justice for Luo Ge.
You have no right to do anything
and harm anyone in the world
with his body.
But I'm Luo Ge now.
I could use his hands
to punish his best brother,
kill his best friend,
and even
marry his favorite woman.
What are you gonna do about me?
I will kill you.
I will kill you!
I'll wipe you out of this world,
without a trace.
It seems that if I don't give you this chance today,
you won't give up.
How about this?
Let's make a bet
that you can kill me.
Immortal Liu Shao.
Okay.
You can rest assured that
I will do it.
If you can't do it,
you'll have to be my wife
and serve me every day.
You can't think of anything else.
Do you dare to say yes?
Okay,
I agree.
Then I'll give you three days.
If you renege on that promise,
or break it later,
I'll make sure your family, friends,
and the Immortal Palace that Luo Ge cares about,
and even the whole Three Realms
die.
I won't stand you up.
In three days,
I will kill you
once and for all.
When my brother came back from the Immortal Palace,
he told me something.
Fu,
one day,
if anything happens to me,
you must do your best
to protect Liu Shao
and help her ascend to the god
to seal the evil spirits.
He and Luo Ge
had already made all kinds of preparations and plans.
So He Na's death
was also part of their plan?
They died
just for
the chance of winning.
Liu Shao.
You are their silver lining.
Don't let them die in vain.
Don't let
the Three Realms,
people,
and friends they're trying to protect
perish in the evil spirits.
For today's plan,
you must refine the Clear Vine as soon as possible,
break through the seal of divine spirit
and ascend to the god,
so as to control that evil thing.
Girl,
I have helped you dredge the meridians with the needle.
It can help the Clear Vine
break the seal,
but it will also make your pain worse.
You have to suck it up.
There's nothing going on in there.
Is everything okay?
I'll go and take a look.
No need.
Let me in.
Let him in.
This
is the real Immortal Master Wanwu.
Supreme God Liu Shao.
It's starting to get interesting.
The three-day wait was not in vain.
The thought of you living three more days
under the name of Luo Ge
makes me sick.
Fortunately,
it ends today.
Luo Ge.
Liu Shao.
I remember I told you.
If you were the God of the Sun,
what would you choose?
I don't want you to waver.
So you kept it from me,
hoping to make me think that
I was splitting
the heart of that evil thing,
not your heart.
Now I'm Luo Ge.
But after tonight, I'll be an evil thing.
I'll bring the Three Realms to an eternal night.
And I'll bring death
to all the people of the world.
Liu Shao.
You know me
and you love me.
You should know that I would rather die
than put myself in that situation.
That evil thing
killed He Na?
Yes.
If you can't do it,
it will kill everyone in the Immortal Palace.
So you've been sober
since He Na died?
You soberly urged me to be the Supreme God,
so that
I could kill you
and seal that evil thing?
I'm sorry.
Only you
can do it.
Did He Na know?
He Na's death
and everything that happened after that
was a plot between He Na and me.
He Na.
Soon,
the Luo Ge you see
may not be the real Luo Ge.
We all have someone to protect,
my people and the demon world,
your immortal palace and the Three Realms.
My days are numbered.
But even if I were to die,
I would not tolerate that evil thing
trampling on those I care about.
I can die,
but I will not tolerate
that evil thing trampling on... in my name
to trample on all that I hold dear.
If we work together,
what chance do we have of winning?
We don't even have a chance.
What?
But if Liu Shao can train herself to be the Supreme God,
she can kill me
and she will be able to pass on the seal of the Sun,
and seal the evil spirits in the Four Seasons Monument.
That way,
the Three Realms and everything we want to protect
and those we value
will be preserved.
Even if Liu Shao were the Supreme God,
she would be no match for that evil spirit.
Besides,
the evil spirit is in your heart.
To cut off the evil spirit
is to cut off your own vitality.
Liu Shao wouldn't have the guts to kill you.
What if
I pretend to be the Black Moonlight
and let her kill me?
She's too smart
to be fooled that easily.
Unless
the real Black Moonlight appears
and kills her most valued friend.
On the night before the wedding,
I could hardly control my evil spirit.
I sealed myself here
to preserve my power.
But I don't know
what happened after that.
He Na had a deal with me.
He said
he would deal with that evil thing.
If he dies,
he will pass his water power to me.
His water energy has the power to clear the mind,
awaken me temporarily.
But it will only last three days at most.
He Na gave his life
to help me get the three days,
so that you could have a chance to become a Supreme God
to seal the evil spirit.
Why?
Why sacrifice the two of you?
Did it ever occur to you that
whether this scheme succeeds or fails,
you will both die?
Our lives are nothing
compared to the peace and security of the Three Realms and the people.
Liu Shao.
I trust you.
You won't fail me and He Na,
right?
You don't have to provoke me.
I don't blame you
for keeping this decision from me.
Because I'm not intending to ask your permission for what I'm about to do either.
for what I'm about to do.
Liu Shao.
If you die,
that evil thing will not necessarily die.
It may break through the seal.
But when I die,
it dies
with me.
Luo Ge.
I remember when you were Lu Li,
♫On rainy days, wind blows smoke♫
you're good at doing calculations.
♫Into circles♫
You know better than I do
♫On both sides, I'm chanting♫
how to choose, don't you?
♫The night is sleepless♫
♫The shadows of the moon are incomplete, and people are in love♫
♫A cocoon of shadows♫
♫Your promise, my fate♫
♫In spring, seasons changed♫
No.
♫But my heart is still the same♫
No!
♫Back to the sky, the clouds passing by♫
The evil spirit is Yin in nature,
♫Is like the things we went through♫
clashes with the sun spirit.
♫Beside the lake, on the boat♫
If you absorb it,
you'll die.
♫The moment we passed each other♫
♫Can compare with the rest of my life♫
I will die.
But Luo Ge
will live.
♫I look at my love and send it to the clouds outside the garden♫
Make your decision.
♫Looking at your ageless face at the end of the world♫
No.
No!
♫You put the winter snow in your ears and can’t hear it♫
Liu Shao.
You are not Sun's shadow.
♫When the flowers stop falling, you and I will miss each other♫
Only you can end this.
♫Everything in the world passes before understanding♫
♫After the missing, my face is still young♫
♫The day the flowers fall in the garden, the day we meet♫
Liu Shao.
♫If you see me for the first time in this life, I'll forever hold it in my heart♫
♫Get lost in your sky♫
♫Whose wilderness♫
Ten thousand years ago,
♫Clouds billow up and fade away in the four seas♫
Sun killed what he loved.
Ten thousand years later,
♫The mountains and rivers after the farewell♫
I can finally protect you.
♫Silence♫
I don't need your protection.
♫Time sighs silently♫
I don't regret it.
♫Whose passing years♫
Don't blame me, okay?
After all,
to live alone
is far crueler than
to die and feel nothing after that.
Liu Shao.
Sorry.
Luo Ge.
No.
Liu Shao.
♫I look at my love and send it to the clouds outside the garden♫
I won't let you die.
I won't.
♫Looking back at the love that still remains in your past life♫
♫The day the flowers fall in the garden, the day we meet♫
I won't let you die.
♫ The year of my life fleets♫
Luo Ge.
♫Whose year is it♫
Can you
fly the wishing lantern with me again?
Liu Shao.
Do you remember what you wished for?
May every day and night from now on be like this moment...
Be now.
May we stay together...
Forever.
I
agree.
In fact,
we've made it.
Look.
We're together now.
It's just that...
my life...
is a little short.
Immortal Luo Ge
kept the oath that day?
How about
Supreme God Luo Ge
make a wish too?
Okay.
I make a wish.
May we be together
forever.
May we never part
day and night.
Agree.
Liu Shao.
Since you agreed,
I believe it.
I'll wait for you forever.
I'll wait for you day and night.
You can't go back on your word.
Don't keep me waiting too long.
Okay?
So...
Supreme God Luo Ge left the Immortal Palace?
Yes.
After he cured Master Zhuo,
he just left
and never went back.
Why didn't he go back?
I heard
♫This is a spring song♫
he was looking for a bird with three feet.
It's the Three-legged Golden Crow,
♫The peach blossoms fly with the swallow♫
the doppelganger of Supreme God Liu Shao.
Someone said that Three-legged Golden Crow
♫Whose lights are light and shine people's way home?♫
was following Supreme God Luo Ge the whole time.
But somehow
Supreme God Luo Ge couldn't seem to see it
and kept looking for it.
♫The clouds roll the sunset♫
No matter how many times it goes around,
♫The moon kisses the eyebrows♫
I will recognize you
♫I am waiting for you to say♫
and follow you
forever.
♫Tonight in this life♫
You can't run away.
♫Ask the flowing water whether it knows the red leaves♫
I won't run away.
I'll never run away.
♫I miss you so much♫
You must follow me forever.
♫I still remember the youth♫
I won't lose you.
♫I laughed and hated getting old♫
♫Flowers bloom alone. The fragrance fills the path♫
♫Look at the stars from faraway♫
♫The chaos of knowing love♫
♫The South Wind folds a little red♫
♫Send you to the Western State♫
♫Wild geese pass the mountains and the sea♫
♫I am rushing to a dream♫
♫The fate of three lifetimes♫
♫Appreciate with our hands tied♫
♫Thousands of paths with flowers♫
♫Flowers bloom alone. The fragrance fills the path♫
♫Look at the stars from faraway♫
♫The chaos of knowing love♫
♫The South Wind folds a little red♫
♫Send you to the Western State♫
♫Wild geese pass the mountains and the sea♫
♫I am rushing to a dream♫
♫The fate of three lifetimes♫
♫Appreciate with our hands tied♫
♫Thousands of paths with flowers♫